One of me, four of you.
我一个，你们四个。
Doesn't seem fair.
看起来不公平。
To you.
对你来说。
Or your kidneys.
对你们的肾脏来说。
[yells]
[大喊]
[dramatic music]
[紧张音乐]
[all grunting]
[所有人哼哼]
♪♪
Time to stop kidney-ing around.
是时候停止肾脏游戏了。
♪♪
Ooh, looks like attack season.
哦，看来是攻击季节了。
I guess I'm gonna have to write you off.
我想我得把你除名了。
[clicks] [beeping]
[点击声] [哔哔声]
[action music]
[动作音乐]
♪♪
[Director] Cut! Great job, Jett.
[导演] 停！干得好，Jett。
Hi. I'm Jett Masterson,
嗨。我是Jett Masterson，
star of "Kidney Punch: One, Two, Three, and Five."
《肾击：一、二、三和五》的明星。
And after a hard day of kidney punching
经过一天辛苦的肾击
and saving the world I could use a vacation.
和拯救世界后，我需要一个假期。
Couldn't you?
难道不是吗？
I know I could, Jett.
我知道我可以，Jett。
- How would you and your family
你和你的家人
like to go on the ultimate family vacation?
想要进行一次终极的
Sure would.
家庭度假吗？
Can't afford it on a kid's salary.
当然愿意。
- For free?
靠孩子的工资可负担不起。
I'm listening.
免费的？
He's not really talking to you.
我在听。
[Jett] If you've ever dreamed of going to Hollywood...
他其实不是在跟你说话。
I'm listening.
我在听。
Then go online, and check out Unique Excursions'
那就上网，查看Unique Excursions的
Ultimate Family Vacation Giveaway today,
终极家庭度假赠品活动今天开始，
because you deserve...
因为你值得...
a break.
休息一下。
[Announcer] To enter the contest,
进入比赛，
go to the Unique Excursions website
前往Unique Excursions网站
and fill out an entry form today.
并今天填写参赛表格。
And now back to Alex Guarnaschelli's
现在回到
"Destination Cook Down."
“目的地烹饪大赛”。
Ooh, now I'm listening.
哦，现在我在听了。
Well, it took all afternoon,
嗯，花了一整个下午，
but the sleeping bags are officially spider free.
但睡袋正式没有蜘蛛了。
Spiders can have them.
蜘蛛可以拥有它们。
No, we are not going on another one
不，我们今年不会再参加
of Dad's stupid camping trips this year.
爸爸那愚蠢的露营旅行了。
We are going to win that Hollywood vacation.
我们要赢得那个好莱坞假期。
Just you wait.
你就等着瞧吧。
We've been waiting forever.
我们已经等了很久了。
I thought playing with these fake beards
我以为玩这些假胡子
would make the time go faster.
会让时间过得更快。
[dog yips]
【狗叫声】
[Dawn] Guys, it's only been three days.
【Dawn】伙计们，才过了三天。
They're gonna call.
他们会打电话来的。
Let's face it.
面对现实吧。
We're going to end up going camping again.
我们最终还是会去露营的。
Just like every year.
就像每年一样。
[phone ringing]
【电话铃声】
Quiet! This is it! It's Unique Excursions!
安静！就是这个！是Unique Excursions！
[all speaking at once]
【大家同时说话】
[Nicky] Oh, my God!
哦，天哪！
All right.
好吧。
Let's play it cool.
让我们保持冷静。
Hey. Hello.
嘿。你好。
Whatevs. 'Sup?
随便。怎么了？
Too cool. Too cool.
太酷了。太酷了。
Hi, I'm Robin from Unique Excursions,
嗨，我是Unique Excursions的Robin，
and I'll tell you what's up.
我会告诉你发生了什么。
You guys are finalists
你们是我们的终极家庭度假赠品的决赛选手。
in our Ultimate Family Vacation Giveaway.
所以告诉我，你们在好莱坞最想做什么？
So tell me, what would you most like to do in Hollywood?
那么告诉我，你在好莱坞最想做什么？
Meet Jett Masterson and punch him in the kidney.
见到杰特·马斯特森并朝他的肾打一拳。
I want to eat at the hottest restaurants
我想在最热门的餐厅用餐
and meet Hollywood's coolest chefs.
并遇见好莱坞最酷的厨师。
How about seeing some world-class magicians?
去看一些世界级的魔术师怎么样？
Please. I want to see celebrities.
拜托，我想看名人。
No, I want to meet celebrities. You know what?
不，我想见名人。你知道吗？
I want to be a celebrity
我想成为名人
and just cruise down Hollywood Boulevard.
然后就在好莱坞大道上兜风。
Oh, in a convertible.
哦，开敞篷车。
We could go to a movie studio.
我们可以去一个电影制片厂。
[Tom] In a convertible.
在敞篷车里。
Oh, and just walk the red carpets
哦，就这样走在红毯上
and work the cameras with one of these and these.
然后拿着这些和这些，与镜头互动。
And then you do--
然后你做——
[Anne] Oh! Dawn, are you okay?
哦！Dawn，你还好吗？
[Tom] Oh, Dawn, are you hurt?
Dawn，你受伤了吗？
Because this is how you could have avoided it.
因为这样你本可以避免的。
Huh?
嗯？
Do a little cheek thing, right?
做一点脸颊的动作，对吧？
And you just stare 'em down.
然后你就盯着他们看。
[Dicky] Nope.
[Dicky]不。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
[all speaking at once]
[所有人同时说话]
Hey, hey!
嘿，嘿！
It doesn't matter,
没关系，
because we're not going to a movie premiere anyway.
因为我们反正不去电影首映。
Yeah, we're meeting Hollywood's coolest chefs.
是的，我们要见好莱坞最酷的厨师。
No, we're meeting Jett Masterson.
不，我们要见Jett Masterson。
Only if he's at a movie premiere.
只有在他参加电影首映时。
Come on! No, no.
快点！不，不。
[all speaking at once]
[所有人同时说话]
Stop! How can a family fight this much?
停！一个家庭怎么能这样争吵？
We're really sorry.
我们真的很抱歉。
Well, I have certainly heard enough.
嗯，我确实听够了。
Yeah.
是啊。
We're sorry we wasted your time.
我们很抱歉浪费了您的时间。
No, I mean it looks like
不，我是说看起来
you guys could really use a vacation.
你们真的需要一个假期。
I know I could.
我知道我需要。
[Anne] Oh!
哦！
[screams]
（尖叫）
[Dicky] Jett Masterson!
杰特·马斯特森！
You guys won.
你们赢了。
You're going to Hollywood!
你们要去好莱坞了！
[all cheering]
（所有人欢呼）
Wait, he's really talking to us this time, right?
等等，这次他真的是在跟我们说话，对吧？
[All] Yes!
（所有人）是的！
[Dicky] We're going to Hollywood!
我们要去好莱坞了！
[all cheering]
（所有人欢呼）
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪♪
[Kids] ♪ Whoo, whoo, Hollywood ♪
[孩子们] ♪哇，哇，好莱坞♪
♪ Whoo, whoo, Hollywood ♪
♪哇，哇，好莱坞♪
You'd think after chanting that song for the past week
你可能会想，经过过去一周一直在唱这首歌
they'd come up with more lyrics.
他们应该会想出更多的歌词。
Oh, there's more. Hit it.
哦，还有更多。开始吧。
[Kids] ♪ Hey, hey, we're in L.A. ♪
[孩子们] ♪嘿，嘿，我们在洛杉矶♪
♪ Hey, hey, we're in L.A. ♪
♪嘿，嘿，我们在洛杉矶♪
[alarm sounds]
[警报声]
[Dawn] Sweet!
太棒了！
Let's grab our luggage, get out of here,
我们拿上行李，离开这里，
and start looking for celebrities.
然后开始寻找名人。
Yeah! Let's go!
好啊！走吧！
[Tom] Oh, look. Perfect timing.
哦，看。时机正好。
[laughs]
（笑）
♪♪
Excuse me, do you know where the limousines are?
打扰一下，你知道豪华轿车在哪里吗？
Sorry. Looking for celebrities.
抱歉。我们在找名人。
Why don't you go ask those photographers?
你为什么不问问那些摄影师呢？
[Photographer] Danielle, over here.
[摄影师] 丹妮尔，这边。
Right here please.
请站这里。
Danielle, can you turn this way please?
丹妮尔，请转向这边好吗？
[Tom] Hey, Dawn, do you have any dental floss in your bag?
[汤姆] 嘿，道恩，你包里有牙线吗？
No, but I have...
没有，但我有...
your wallet and mom's purse for some reason.
你的钱包和妈妈的包，不知为何。
They're taking up half of my bag.
它们占了我包的一半。
Yeah, and they're heavy.
是啊，而且很重。
Why do you think we don't want to carry 'em?
你以为我们为什么不想带它们？
[Anne] Yeah.
[安妮] 是啊。
[Tom] Our bags should be here any minute.
我们的行李应该随时会到。
Yep.
是的。
Any minute.
随时会到。
Where are our bags?
我们的行李在哪儿？
Where's Dicky?
迪基在哪儿？
[Dawn] What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Shh!
嘘！
I'm trying to catch the penguin.
我正试着抓企鹅。
[Tom] Would you get off of there!
你能不能从那上面下来！
[Anne] Okay, let's just go to the airline counter
好吧，我们直接去航空公司的柜台
and ask them where they are.
并询问他们的位置。
Get down.
下来。
[playful music]
[欢快的音乐]
I'm really sorry, sir. I--
真的很抱歉，先生。我——
You should be more careful.
你应该更小心些。
A lot of strange people in Hollywood.
好莱坞有很多奇怪的人。
They were accidentally loaded onto the wrong plane,
它们被意外地装上了错误的飞机，
but they should be here in 3 to 30 business days.
但它们应该在3到30个工作日内到达这里。
Thank you for choosing West Coast Airlines.
感谢您选择西海岸航空公司。
Have a nice day!
祝您有个愉快的一天！
Did she say "3 to 30?"
她刚才是说“3到30天”吗？
Ricky's starting to panic.
瑞奇开始慌了。
[Anne] No, no. It's going to be okay, honey.
[安妮] 不，不。会没事的，亲爱的。
You're right.
你说得对。
I've gone 3 to 30 days without clean underwear before.
我曾经有过3到30天没换干净内裤的经历。
You know, and I am sure
你知道，我确信
Unique Excursions will take care of us.
Unique Excursions会照顾我们的。
Am I right?
对吧？
Yeah, that's the spirit.
没错，就是这样。
Yeah, we're Harpers.
是的，我们是哈珀一家。
And the Harpers don't let anything ruin their vacation.
哈珀家的人不会让任何事情破坏他们的假期。
Yeah! Bring it in.
耶！来吧。
[All] Whoa, Harpers!
哇，哈珀家！
Whoa, it's the Harpers.
哇，是哈珀家。
[All] Robin!
罗宾！
[Anne] We are so happy to see you.
我们见到你太高兴了。
Me too.
我也是。
So here's the thing.
所以，事情是这样的。
You know how you need money to run a company?
你知道经营一家公司需要钱吗？
Well, apparently we don't have any,
嗯，显然我们没有钱，
so I regret to inform you that your vacation is over.
所以我很遗憾地通知你，你的假期结束了。
[all protesting in confusion]
[众人困惑地抗议]
But all we got to see was the baggage carousel.
但我们只看到了行李传送带。
[Robin] Well, that's fun.
[Robin] 嗯，那挺有趣的。
Anyhoo, on a completely unrelated note
总之，说个完全不相关的事
I have to go catch a flight to Mexico, so adios.
我得去赶飞往墨西哥的航班，所以再见。
[all speaking at once]
[众人同时说话]
Okay, a little hiccup, but hey,
好吧，有点小插曲，但嘿，
we're still in Hollywood, right? You know, we're already here,
我们还在好莱坞，对吧？你知道，我们已经在这儿了，
so we might as well make the best of it.
所以我们不妨充分利用它。
You know what? You are right again, honey.
你知道吗？你又对了，亲爱的。
Nothing is gonna stop this family
没有什么能阻止我们一家人
from having a great vacation.
度过一个美好的假期。
All right, toss me my wallet, and let's get out of here.
好吧，把我的钱包扔给我，我们离开这里。
All right.
好的。
Um, this isn't my bag.
嗯，这不是我的包。
No problem. Is my wallet in that bag?
没问题。我的钱包在那包里吗？
It is not.
不在。
Wait a minute. So we're in Hollywood
等一下。所以我们现在在好莱坞
with no clothes, no money, and nowhere to go?
没有衣服，没有钱，也没有地方可去？
[Anne] I'll go talk to the airlines
[Anne] 我去和航空公司谈谈，
and see if maybe they can get us home.
看看他们是否能让我们回家。
No, let's not give up yet.
不，我们不要放弃。
Wait a minute.
等等。
The owner of this bag probably has Dawn's bag, right?
这个包的主人可能拿着Dawn的包，对吧？
Maybe there's something inside that'll tell us who they are,
也许里面有什么东西能告诉我们他们是谁，
and we can get Dawn's bag back!
这样我们就能拿回Dawn的包了！
Okay.
好的。
Oh!
哦！
Breath spray.
口气清新喷雾。
Smoke pellets?
烟雾弹？
A key.
一把钥匙。
Clean underwear?
干净的 underwear？
Dibs!
我要了！
Ooh.
哦。
"Do not pull."
不要拉。
It says "Do not pull."
上面写着‘不要拉’。
Oh, here's something.
哦，这里有点东西。
It's a reservation for someone named Dave Olschewski
这是给一个叫Dave Olschewski的人今天中午在魔法城堡的预订。
for the Magic Castle today at noon.
魔法城堡。
The Magic Castle.
That's the premier showcase
那是顶级魔术师的展示舞台
for top magicians from around the world!
来自世界各地的顶尖魔术师！
Maybe we should go there and see if he shows up with the bag?
也许我们应该去那里看看他是否带着包出现？
You know, just saying.
你知道，只是说说。
Actually that's not a bad idea.
实际上，这不是个坏主意。
Tom, what do you think?
汤姆，你怎么看？
I think it's settled.
我想就这么定了。
To the Magic Castle!
去魔法城堡！
Oh, we've been walking for hours.
哦，我们已经走了好几个小时了。
So thirsty!
好渴啊！
Come on, Anne. We're almost there.
加油，安妮。我们快到了。
I'm pushing just as hard as I can!
我已经尽全力在走了！
Look, it's the Magic Castle!
看，那就是魔法城堡！
[Tom] Oh!
哦！
Check it out.
看看这个。
Someone's flying a drone.
有人在飞无人机。
Hollywood has everything.
好莱坞什么都有。
Yeah, yeah. People are magical. Things fly.
是啊，是啊。人们都很神奇。东西都能飞。
Now, let's find Olschewski and get my bag back.
现在，我们得找到奥尔舍夫斯基，把我的包拿回来。
I saw that guy at the airport.
我在机场看到那个家伙了。
[Ricky] He's got your bag.
他拿了你的包。
He bumped into me.
他撞到我了。
That must have been when our bags got switched.
那一定是我们行李被调换的时候。
[Nicky] Then he must be Olschewski.
那他一定是奥尔舍夫斯基。
Let's go! Come on, go, go, go!
我们走吧！快点，走，走，走！
[Tom] Oh, ow, wow.
哦，哎哟，哇。
That's a big hill. Come on. Go.
那是个大山坡。快点。走。
Whoo!
哇！
Excuse me, where's the guy who just came in here?
打扰一下，刚刚进来的那个人在哪里？
No one came in here.
没有人进来这里。
[Tom] Do you have any water?
[Tom] 你有水吗？
But that's impossible. We saw him walk in.
但那是不可能的。我们看见他走进来了。
Cold water, warm water, wet sponge?
冷水，温水，湿海绵？
Sorry, sir, all the beverages and sponges are inside.
对不起，先生，所有的饮料和海绵都在里面。
Then we'd like to go inside, please.
那我们想进去，请。
Yes, we would.
是的，我们会的。
I'm afraid nobody's allowed in without a reservation.
恐怕没有预约的人是不允许进入的。
Reservation.
预约。
Dad, you have a reservation.
爸爸，你有预约。
Yes.
是的。
I have a reservation?
我有预订吗？
Ricky, get the reservation.
Ricky，拿预订信息。
Ha, the reservation.
哈，预订信息。
One reservation coming right up.
预订信息马上就来。
Iugh.
呃。
Whoops.
哎呀。
The reservation.
预订信息。
Mr. Olschewski. Welcome back.
Olschewski先生。欢迎回来。
That's right. That's me.
没错。那就是我。
Mr. Olschewski.
奥尔舍夫斯基先生。
Yeah.
是的。
Well, I'm sure you remember
嗯，我确信你记得
that there is a dress code for adults,
成人有dress code，
but I see here
但我在这里看到
that you left your jacket on your last visit.
你上次来时把外套留在这里了。
How did it fit in there?
它在那里面怎么放的？
It's not even wrinkled.
甚至都没有皱。
This is the Magic Castle.
这里是魔法城堡。
You may all go in.
你们都可以进去了。
I'll check your bags.
我会检查你们的包。
[Anne] Thank you.
[安妮] 谢谢你。
In where?
在哪里？
Don't worry. I got this.
别担心。我搞得定。
Open sesame!
芝麻开门！
Dude, you are way cooler in Hollywood.
伙计，你在好莱坞酷多了。
[Harpers] Wow!
[哈珀斯] 哇！
[playful music]
[欢快的音乐]
This place is amazing.
这个地方太神奇了。
It is, but we have to find Olschewski and get my bag back.
确实，但我们得找到奥尔舍夫斯基并拿回我的包。
Maybe we should split up.
也许我们应该分开行动。
Nicky, Dicky, go with Mom. I'll go with Ricky and Dad.
尼基，迪基，跟妈妈走。我和瑞奇还有爸爸一起。
Dad?
爸爸？
They made him disappear.
他们让他消失了。
He's right there.
他就在那儿。
- Keep 'em coming.
继续来。
Okay, good luck, honey.
好的，祝你好运，亲爱的。
You too. Let's go, boys.
你也是。我们走吧，孩子们。
[Tom] You wouldn't by any chance have any dental floss
汤姆]你不会碰巧有牙线吧？
back there, would you? I got a thing in my teeth.
我牙缝里卡了东西。
There he is! Come on, Dad.
他来了！快点，爸爸。
- Oh, sorry. I'm cool.
哦，对不起。我没事。
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
He went in there. Come on!
他进去了。快点！
[Tom] Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
And now for my next trick
现在轮到我的下一个魔术了
I shall make three people interrupt my show.
我要让三个人打断我的表演。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Whoops.
哎呀。
The Great Billini!
伟大的比林尼！
I've read all your books.
我读过你所有的书。
And we're really sorry to interrupt,
我们真的很抱歉打断你，
but we're looking for a man who just came in here.
但我们正在找刚刚进来的一个人。
You know, kind of thin. Carrying a bag?
你知道，有点瘦。拿着一个包？
Ta-da!
塔-达！
[applause]
[掌声]
No, not him.
不，不是他。
While we're here could you pull something out of my teeth?
既然我们在这里，你能帮我从牙齿里弄点东西出来吗？
I just got a little something in there.
我刚刚卡了点东西在里面。
Let me see what I can do. Just one second.
让我看看我能做什么。稍等一下。
[choking sounds] [coughing]
[哽咽声] [咳嗽]
[applause]
[掌声]
No, that's not it, but could I?
不，不是那个，但可以吗？
Yes.
可以。
No, this man was wearing a--
不，这个人当时戴着——
No, actually the only people
不，实际上唯一
to interrupt my show are you guys,
打断我表演的只有你们，
which means that you get to help me in my next trick.
这意味着你们得帮我完成下一个魔术。
You know, we really don't have any time to--
你知道，我们真的没有时间——
We can spare a minute.
我们可以腾出一分钟。
Here we go. A regular deck of 98 cards.
开始了。一副普通的98张牌。
You know what we call this? Showing off.
你知道我们怎么称呼这个吗？炫耀。
Ooh, hang on. Got it. Ha!
哦，等等。拿到了。哈！
No, actually I need you to take the cards and take out any--
不，实际上我需要你拿起这些牌，然后抽出任何——
Wait, wait.
等等，等等。
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
[laughter]
[笑声]
Take out any card that you want.
抽出任何你想要的牌。
And then for you, I have this.
然后，为了你，我准备了这支。
This is a very special magic pen.
这是一支非常特别的魔术笔。
Look, it's gone. It's back.
看，它消失了。它又回来了。
It's invisible ink.
这是隐形的墨水。
Take the pen.
拿笔。
Okay! Could I have your card?
好的！可以给我你的牌吗？
Ace of hearts. Excellent choice.
红心A。非常好的选择。
Sign your name across the face of the card.
在牌面上签上你的名字。
I know this trick. I read it in your book!
我知道这个魔术。我在你的书里读到过！
Oh, good, 'cause I can't remember
哦，太好了，因为我记不清
how it ends, so maybe you could help me?
它是怎么结束的，所以也许你可以帮我？
Why don't you try and stop me?
你为什么不试着阻止我？
Watch closely as I make this card disappear.
请仔细看，我将让这张牌消失。
[audience gasps]
[观众惊叹]
What?
什么？
[applause]
[掌声]
Wow, now before we make the card reappear,
哇，在我们让牌重新出现之前，
I kind of fancy a little bit of a snack.
我有点想吃点小零食。
How about you?
你呢？
Definitely.
当然。
You, sir, do you have any snacks for us?
先生，您有零食给我们吗？
Perhaps in your pocket?
或许在您的口袋里？
Ricky, you know I don't have any snacks--
Ricky，你知道我没有带任何零食——
[applause] Oh!
哦！
[Magician] Careful.
小心。
Don't want to lose this, Mr. Olschewski.
不想弄丢这个，Olschewski先生。
Yes, I am Mr. Olschewski.
是的，我是Olschewski先生。
Would you mind opening that sealed bag of chips?
您介意打开那包密封的薯片吗？
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
It's my card!
这是我的牌！
[applause] [Tom] It's her card.
（掌声）（Tom）是她的牌。
Impossible.
不可能。
And now for the big finish.
现在进入高潮部分。
[Both] One, two--
一，二——
Olschewski!
奥尔舍夫斯基！
[Both] Three!
三！
[applause]
掌声
Where'd he go?
他去哪儿了？
[Nicky] We can't find him.
我们找不到他。
He was just here. He must have gone that way.
他刚才还在这里。一定是往那边走了。
[Tom] Let's go.
我们走吧。
How did Olschewski just disappear?
奥尔舍夫斯基怎么就这样消失了？
Hey, old-dudesky's getting into a cab.
嘿，老头儿上出租车了。
[all yelling at once]
[众人同时喊叫]
[Dawn] You have my bag!
[Dawn] 你拿了我的包！
[all groan]
[众人呻吟]
We have to follow him!
我们必须跟着他！
How? We don't have a car.
怎么跟？我们没有车。
No, but Olschewski does.
不，但Olschewski有。
That's Olschewski's valet ticket.
那是Olschewski的停车票。
Um, excuse me. Please hurry.
呃，劳驾。请快点。
Kids, I know you want to keep tracking this man down,
孩子们，我知道你们想继续追踪这个人，
but we can't just take someone's car.
但是，我们不能随便开别人的车。
[loud rock music]
[大声的摇滚音乐]
Holy rolling thunder.
天哪，雷鸣般的滚动。
Mr. Olschewski. Your car.
奥尔舍夫斯基先生。您的车。
I'm sorry. It's not my car.
对不起。这不是我的车。
[All] Dad?
[所有人] 爸爸？
[all whispering at once]
[所有人同时低声说]
It's our car.
这是我们的车。
[Ricky] Yes!
[瑞奇] 太好了！
Ha-ha. Trunk, please.
哈哈。请打开后备箱。
Ooh, fuzzy dice.
哦，毛绒骰子。
I don't see the cab.
我没看到出租车。
Great. Now we'll never find him.
太好了。现在我们永远找不到他了。
Well, now what are we supposed to do, Tom?
那么，我们现在该怎么办，汤姆？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I can't think and drive at the same time.
我无法同时思考和开车。
Well, that's reassuring!
那真是令人安心！
Wait. Maybe his GPS will have his address.
等等。也许他的GPS会有他的地址。
Worth a shot. Okay, addresses. Here we go.
值得一试。好的，地址。我们开始吧。
[GPS Woman] One address found.
（GPS女声）找到一个地址。
Okay there's one saved address.
好的，这里有一个保存的地址。
I bet that address will lead us right to Olschewski.
我打赌这个地址会直接带我们找到Olschewski。
And my bag.
还有我的包。
Ha-ha! Here.
哈哈！这里。
Hold the dice. Seatbelts!
拿着骰子。系好安全带！
[Anne] Okay.
[Anne] 好的。
[GPS Woman] Proceed to Hollywood Boulevard.
[GPS Woman] 前往好莱坞大道。
[Ricky] Ooh, Hollywood Boulevard.
[Ricky] 哦，好莱坞大道。
[Dawn] How do I look?
[Dawn] 我看起来怎么样？
[Anne] Sunglasses.
[Anne] 戴上墨镜。
♪ Next up, Hollywood Workin' on my tan ♪
♪ 接下来，好莱坞，努力晒黑 ♪
♪ While makin' my plan now Next up, Hollywood, C-A ♪
♪ 同时制定我的计划，接下来，好莱坞，C-A ♪
♪ Next up, Hollywood ♪
♪ 接下来，好莱坞 ♪
Ooh, Hollywood and Vine!
哦，好莱坞和藤街！
♪ Pedal to the metal, gonna run this engine raw ♪
♪ 油门踩到底，要让这引擎狂奔 ♪
Oh, Hollywood Wax Museum!
哦，好莱坞蜡像馆！
♪ Three, two, one, blastoff ♪
♪ 三，二，一，发射 ♪
Ooh, Hollywood Walk of Fame!
哦，好莱坞星光大道！
Ooh, New York Pizza!
哦，纽约披萨！
Dad, you've gone too far.
爸爸，你开过头了。
Oh, I'm not slowing this beast down.
哦，我可不会让这大家伙减速。
This California breeze feels too good in my mane.
这加州的微风拂过我的鬃毛，感觉太棒了。
Ouch. Honey, your mane's getting kind of sun burnt.
哎哟。亲爱的，你的鬃毛好像有点晒伤了。
Ah.
啊。
Ooh, sorry.
哦，对不起。
Ooh, the Hollywood sign. Selfie!
哦，好莱坞标志。自拍！
See if the sun can catch me now.
看看太阳现在能不能追上我。
Ooh!
哦！
Dang it, Dad.
该死的，爸爸。
[Dicky] Guys, look. Jett Masterson's new movie!
[迪基]伙计们，看。杰特·马斯特森的新电影！
[All] Ooh!
哦！
♪ Three, two, one, blastoff ♪
♪ 三、二、一，发射 ♪
Told you I look just like him.
我告诉过你我看起来和他一模一样。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
♪ And it's three, two, one, blastoff ♪
♪ 三、二、一，发射 ♪
[GPS Woman] You have reached your destination.
您已到达目的地。
Where are we?
我们在哪儿？
Weren't you listening?
你没在听吗？
We're at your destination.
我们已经到了你的目的地。
Tom, what do you think this place is?
汤姆，你认为这个地方是什么？
I don't know, but from the smell of it
我不知道，但闻起来像是
it's where raccoons go to poop.
浣熊来这里拉屎的地方。
So what do we do now?
那我们现在怎么办？
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
I got this.
我有办法。
Do not pull.
不要拉。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
There's the key in the bag.
钥匙在包里。
Maybe it's for the door.
可能是用来开门的。
Only one way to find out.
只有一种方法能知道。
[Anne] But, Dawn, you can't just go in there.
[Anne] 但是，Dawn，你不能就这样进去。
She went in! Come on. Come on.
她进去了！快点，快点。
[Dawn] Hello?
[Dawn] 有人吗？
[Dicky] Wait, wait, wait, Dawn.
[Dicky] 等等，等等，等等，Dawn。
Wait, don't--
等等，别——
[Dawn] Shh.
[Dawn] 嘘。
[door clangs shut] [gasping]
[门砰的一声关上] [喘气声]
[All] Uh-oh.
[所有人] 哎呀。
[evil laughs]
[邪恶的笑声]
Uh-oh!
哎呀！
Hello, Olschewski.
你好，奥尔舍夫斯基。
[All] Uh-oh?
哎呀？
All right, start talking.
好吧，开始说吧。
[all speaking at once]
（大家同时说话）
Stop talking!
别说了！
Very clever cover, Olschewski.
真是巧妙的伪装，奥尔舍夫斯基。
Pretending to be a family man.
假装成一个家庭男人。
You might have overdone it a bit.
你可能有点过头了。
Four kids?
四个孩子？
Tell me about it. Wait, Tom?
跟我说说。等等，汤姆？
Oh, sorry.
哦，对不起。
Listen, Mr. Thug.
听着，先生。
The name's Gayle.
我叫盖尔。
[all stifling laughs]
（所有人都忍住笑）
It's a family name.
这是个家族名字。
[all giggle]
（所有人都咯咯笑）
My father's name was Gayle,
我父亲的名字是盖尔，
and his father's name was Gayle,
我祖父的名字也是盖尔，
and his father before him. All Gayles.
再往前也是盖尔。全是盖尔。
[laughter]
（笑声）
Oh-- Okay. All right.
哦——好吧。好吧。
Everyone laugh at the guy with the funny name.
大家都笑那个名字滑稽的家伙。
[all laugh]
（大家都笑）
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
哈哈哈哈。
Laugh time is over!
笑够了！
[Goon] Let's go.
（打手）我们走。
All right, all right. Listen...
好吧，好吧。听着……
this is all just a big mix-up.
这一切都是个大误会。
I mean we're the Harpers.
我是说我们是哈珀一家。
We're just a normal family trying to have a vacation.
我们只是一个普通的家庭，正努力享受假期。
Oh.
哦。
Oh. Oh.
哦。哦。
Well, no one's going on vacation
好吧，没人能去度假
until I get the thumb drive!
直到我拿到那个U盘！
The thumb drive?
U盘？
The thumb drive!
U盘！
Not the thumb drive.
不是U盘。
What's a thumb drive?
U盘是什么？
Really?
真的吗？
I can't believe you don't know what a thumb drive is.
我真不敢相信你不知道U盘是什么。
What's a thumb drive?
什么是U盘？
A thumb drive stores computer files.
U盘用于存储电脑文件。
Yeah. Olschewski must have information they want.
是的，Olschewski肯定有他们想要的信息。
I'm telling you, you got us confused with someone else.
我告诉你，你把我们和别人搞混了。
Yeah, yeah, we are not thumb drive people.
是啊，我们不是用U盘的人。
And she's right. We don't even use 'em.
她说得对，我们甚至都不用它们。
Don't even like to drive. Never.
甚至不喜欢开车，从来没有。
Wish I didn't have thumbs.
真希望我没有拇指。
Overrated. What is the point?
被高估了，有什么意义呢？
I'm not here to play games, Olschewski.
我不是来这里玩游戏的，Olschewski。
Dang it.
该死。
Playing games was our last hope.
玩游戏是我们最后的希望。
There's got to be some way out of this.
一定有办法摆脱这个困境。
Ricky?
里基？
Oh, sure.
哦，当然。
When it involves a puppet show or getting the stain
当涉及到木偶戏或去除球衣上的污渍时，你总有答案。
out of a jersey you've got all the answers.
我知道该怎么做。
I know what to do.
是时候给这个聚会增添一点活力了。
It's time to bring a little punch to this party.
迪基，不要。
Dicky, no.
迪基，是的。
Dicky, yes.
All I need are the smoke pellets from Olschewski's bag.
我只需要从奥尔舍夫斯基的包里拿些烟雾弹。
Dicky, don't do anything stupid.
迪基，别做傻事。
Stupid is my middle name.
傻事就是我的中间名。
[Dawn] Don't you dare. Don't you dare. I swear!
[道恩] 你敢试试。你敢试试。我发誓！
[Tom] Listen, Gayle, tell you what.
[汤姆] 听着，盖尔，告诉你吧。
You let us go...
你让我们走...
the second we get back to Boulder,
我们一回到博尔德，
12 pack of tube socks coming your way.
就给你送来一打管袜。
And that is just the beginning.
而这只是开始。
Honey, don't--
亲爱的，别——
Let the man respond to the offer.
让他说完这个提议。
[Anne] I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起，对不起。
Raccoon!
浣熊！
Hey, tough guys,
嘿，硬汉们，
today's forecast is cloudy with a chance...
今天的天气预报是多云，有可能会……
of pain.
疼痛。
[grunts]
嗯？
What?
什么？
[Goon] Oh!
哦！
Oh!
Hey, Olschewski, control your kid.
嘿，奥尔舍夫斯基，管好你的孩子。
Do you have kids, Gayle?
盖尔，你有孩子吗？
Looks like we should call this a tie.
看来我们应该宣布平局。
[Gayle] What the-- Waht the--
盖尔]搞什么——搞什么——
Run! Go, go!
跑！快，快！
[Tom] Go, go, go, go, go!
汤姆]快，快，快，快，快！
Go, go, go, go, go!
快，快，快，快，快！
My job must be done here,
我的工作必须在这里完成，
because it's time to... punch out!
因为现在是时候……打卡下班了！
[Dawn] Come on!
快点！
Oh.
哦。
Ah!
啊！
[tires screech]
That. Was. Awesome!
那。真是。太棒了！
- Woah. - I was so scared. - [Dicky] That was close.
- 哇。 - 我吓坏了。 - [迪基] 好险。
[Nicky] Who were those people?
[尼基] 那些人是谁？
[Ricky] What's going on?
[里基] 发生什么事了？
[Tom] Okay. I think we lost 'em.
[汤姆] 好了。我想我们甩掉他们了。
Let's just call the police.
我们还是报警吧。
[cell phone rings] It's Gayle's phone.
[手机铃声] 是Gayle的手机。
Not it!
不是我！
[Ricky] Don't give it to me!
[Ricky] 别给我！
I don't want it.
我不想要。
Hey, I don't want it either.
嘿，我也不想要。
[Nicky] No, no. Seriously?
[Nicky] 不，不。真的吗？
[Man] Hello?
你好？
Should I answer?
我应该接吗？
[Man] Yes, this is the CIA.
是的，这是中央情报局。
How can they hear me?
他们怎么能听到我？
[Man] You're whispering very loudly, Mr. Harper.
你其实可以小声点，哈珀先生。
We need to get your family to safety.
我们需要确保你的家人安全。
How did you know we had this phone?
你们怎么知道我们有这部电话？
[Man] Ma'am, we're the CIA. Now you can't go to the police.
女士，我们是中央情报局。现在你不能去找警察。
They've been infiltrated by Gayle's men.
他们已经被盖尔的人渗透了。
Wait, what is going on? Who is Gayle?
等等，到底发生了什么？谁是盖尔？
Yeah. Who's Olschewski?
对啊，奥尔舍夫斯基又是谁？
[Man] Let's just say you've been caught up
这么说吧，你已经卷入了一些国际间谍活动。
in some international spy business.
涉及到了一些国际间谍事务。
[all gasp]
[所有人都倒吸一口凉气]
No need to gasp. You're safe now.
不必惊讶。你现在安全了。
Just come in, and we'll protect you.
进来吧，我们会保护你。
I'm sending directions to the GPS.
我正在发送定位到GPS。
We'll contact you with further instructions.
我们会与你联系，提供进一步的指示。
No, but--
不，但是——
[dial tone]
[拨号音]
[beeps]
[哔声]
Wow. We finally caught a break, huh?
哇。我们终于有了转机，是吧？
[Ricky and Dicky] Yes.
[Ricky和Dicky] 是的。
Drive fast, Tom.
开快点，Tom。
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
[hurried, tense music]
[急促紧张的音乐]
[GPS Woman] Turn left on North Windsor Boulevard.
[GPS女声] 在北温莎大道左转。
You have reached your destination.
您已到达目的地。
[All] Whoa.
[所有人] 哇。
[Anne] Paramount Pictures? This is so exciting!
[安妮] 派拉蒙影业？这太令人兴奋了！
[laughing]
[笑声]
Okay.
好的。
Gate's not opening.
大门没有打开。
Why isn't the gate opening?
为什么大门没有打开？
Okay. All right, all right, all right.
好的。好吧，好吧，好吧。
Here's the plan.
计划是这样的。
Run for it!
跑吧！
Dad, wait!
爸爸，等等！
I've got some Hollywood magic of my own.
我也有自己的好莱坞魔法。
Watch and learn, boys. Mom, glasses.
看着学着，孩子们。妈妈，眼镜。
Oh.
哦。
Be right with you.
马上就来。
Hi.
嗨。
Yoo-hoo, my fellow Hollywooder.
哟，我的好莱坞同道。
Yes, it's me, Dawn Harper, the famous movie actor.
是的，是我，Dawn Harper，著名电影演员。
[giggles] Please, no autographs.
[咯咯笑]请不要签名。
Anyway, I'm here for a very important meeting with Steve...
无论如何，我来这里是为了与Steve进行一个非常重要的会议...
Paramount,
派拉蒙，
so if you would just be a doll
所以如果你能帮忙
and open the gate that'd be divine.
打开那扇门，那就太好了。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
"Divine?" Seriously?
“太好了？”认真的吗？
We're doomed.
我们完蛋了。
Oh!
哦！
Much obliged.
非常感谢。
[Anne] We're in.
[Anne] 我们进来了。
[Ricky] We're saved!
[Ricky] 我们得救了！
[Dicky] Yeah, but what are we supposed to do
[Dicky] 是啊，但我们该做什么
while Dawn's here in a meeting with Steve Paramount?
当Dawn在这里和Steve Paramount开会时？
[all groan]
[众人叹气]
[Tom] Where is this guy?
[Tom] 这家伙在哪里？
His text said to meet him right at this bench.
他的短信说就在这个长椅上见他。
Oh, my gosh. That's Jack Griffo.
哦，天哪。那是Jack Griffo。
[Nicky] He's walking this way!
[Nicky] 他正朝这边走来！
[Dicky] He's getting closer.
他越来越近了。
He's sitting down.
他坐下了。
I'm talking right to him.
我正直接跟他说话。
Hi.
嗨。
[all gasp]
大家都惊呼。
No need to gasp.
不必惊讶。
[gasps] You're the guy on the phone.
你就是在电话里的那个人。
You're our contact?
你是我们的联系人？
But you're Max Thunderman.
但你不是Max Thunderman吗？
I mean, you know, the kids watch the show.
我的意思是，你知道，孩子们都看那个节目。
We love it. We do.
我们很喜欢，真的。
That's just my cover.
那只是我的掩护。
In real life, I work for the CIA.
实际上，我在为中央情报局工作。
I'm here to help, all right?
我是来帮忙的，好吗？
So just hand me over the thumb drive,
所以把那个U盘交给我，
and I'll take care of everything else.
我会处理剩下的一切。
We don't have the thumb drive.
我们没有那个U盘。
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Look, Harpers, I don't know who you're working for,
听着，哈珀一家，我不知道你们为谁工作，
but I want that drive.
但我想要那个U盘。
We don't work for anybody.
我们不为任何人工作。
[Anne] We own a sporting goods shop.
我们拥有一家体育用品店。
Oh, can we interest you in some half-off tube socks?
哦，我们有打对折的袜子，您感兴趣吗？
Ex-nay on the tube socks-ay.
别提袜子的事。
Give me the drive, old man.
把驱动器给我，老头。
Aah.
啊。
Guys, I don't think he really works for the CIA.
伙计们，我觉得他不太像是为CIA工作的。
I'm gonna give you three seconds.
我给你三秒钟时间。
Things are gonna get ugly,
事情会变得很难看，
and with this face it's not easy.
而且用这张脸来做这事可不容易。
Three, two--
三，二——
He's counting.
他在倒数。
Wait. I have it right here.
等等。我这里就有。
Are you sure you really want it?
你确定你真的想要它吗？
Yes. Give it to me.
是的。给我。
All right. One thumb drive coming right up!
好的。一个U盘马上来！
Ahh!
啊！
[Dawn] Run!
[Dawn] 跑！
[Tom] You just blinded Max Thunderman!
[Tom] 你刚刚让Max Thunderman失明了！
[Anne] Dawn, I can't believe you did that!
[Anne] Dawn，我真不敢相信你做了那件事！
Nice work!
干得好！
Henchmen!
手下们！
Yes, sir?
是的，先生？
[Jack] Go get them! Go!
杰克]去抓住他们！快！
Gah!
啊！
[Dicky] Hey, look. The drone.
迪基]嘿，看。那架无人机。
[Anne] Don't look at the drone. Look at the octopus.
安妮]别看无人机。看那只章鱼。
[Tom] What octopus?
汤姆]什么章鱼？
Ugh, tentacles.
呃，触手。
Split up!
分开行动！
[Anne] Go, go, go. Go in there.
快，快，快。进去那里。
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
快点，快点，快点！
I hate octopus.
我讨厌章鱼。
[gasps] Ooh, the Hollywood sign!
哦，好莱坞标志！
Oh, dang it! I got monkey-bombed.
哦，糟糕！我被猴子炸弹炸了。
Come on!
快点！
Sorry.
对不起。
Henchmen! Fruit!
手下！水果！
[Nicky] They're right behind us!
他们就在我们后面！
I know, I know, I know! Ooh, in here.
我知道，我知道，我知道！哦，这里。
Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
Wow, there are beaches everywhere in L.A.
哇，洛杉矶到处都是海滩。
[Dawn] Uh, I don't think this is a real beach.
[Dawn] 呃，我觉得这不是真正的海滩。
[Nicky] The beach may not be real,
[Nicky] 海滩可能不是真的，
but she is.
但她确实是。
Alex Guarnaschelli!
Alex Guarnaschelli！
He's right. I am real.
他说得对。我是真的。
On this delicious beach-themed episode
在这个美味海滩主题的节目中
of Alex Guarnaschelli's "Destination Cook Down."
Alex Guarnaschelli的'目的地烹饪对决'。
[tropical music plays]
[热带音乐播放]
Oh, this is a dream come true. Nicky Harper.
哦，这简直是梦想成真。Nicky Harper。
Boulder, Colorado. I love you.
Boulder，科罗拉多州。我爱你。
He does.
他确实如此。
So much, but it's a shame he's got to go.
非常爱，但遗憾的是他得走了。
[Tom] Come on.
来吧。
But I want to stay and watch.
但我想要留下来观看。
Watch? Oh, no. You're not watching.
观看？哦，不。你不是在观看。
You're cooking on "Destination Cook Down"
你是在《目的地烹饪对决》上烹饪
with today's special guest judge, Ciara.
与今天的特别嘉宾评委Ciara一起。
[tropical music plays]
热带音乐响起
Ciara?
席亚拉？
Wait, Nicky, we have to go!
等等，尼基，我们得走了！
No. Ricky has his magic, and I have mine,
不。里基有他的魔法，我也有我的，
and I'm taking this chef down.
我今天要打败这位厨师。
Kid, I've beaten eggs bigger than you,
小子，我打败过的蛋比你个头还大，
so let's get this beach party started
所以让我们用今天的特别食材
with today's special ingredient
和我女儿阿瓦的最爱...
and my daughter Ava's favorite...
章鱼！
Octopus!
[热带音乐播放]
[tropical music plays]
[Nicky] Ooh, octopus.
哦，章鱼。
She's got legs, and I know how to use 'em.
它有腿，我知道怎么用它们。
["Wipe Out" playing]
[《Wipe Out》播放]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧性音乐]
[Ricky] Over here!
[Ricky] 这边！
[Dicky] Through this door!
[Dicky] 通过这扇门！
[Anne] Go, go, go!
[Anne] 快，快，快！
[Dicky] This door.
[Dicky] 这扇门。
[Anne] In here. Come on, guys.
[Anne] 这里。快点，伙计们。
[all panting]
[所有人喘气]
[All] Whoa!
哇！
[Anne] This must be the prop room.
这一定是道具室。
Look, it's the Hyperion laser ray
看，这是《乌尔比娜之旅》中的Hyperion激光枪。
from "The Journey to Urbina."
我希望它是真的。
I wish it were real.
我们现在确实可以使用一些毁灭性的激光力量。
We could sure use some devastating laser power
（嗡嗡声）
right now.
耶！
[whirring]
抱歉。
Yeah!
上面写着“不要推”。
Sorry.
迪奇！
It was labeled "Do not push."
上面标着“不要按。”
[Anne and Ricky] Dicky!
[Anne和Ricky] Dicky！
Toast more tortillas!
再烤些玉米饼！
Yes, Chef.
是的，主厨。
Season the peppers.
给辣椒调味。
[Dawn] Yes, Chef.
[Dawn] 是的，主厨。
I've got the octopus.
我拿到章鱼了。
["Wipe Out" continues]
[“Wipe Out”继续播放]
Dad, brow!
爸爸，眉毛！
Yes, Chef.
是的，主厨。
[gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
No way!
不可能！
Hey, hey, kids.
嘿，嘿，孩子们。
I do a really good impression.
我模仿得很像。
[bad SpongeBob impression] "Hey, Ricky and Dicky,
[糟糕的海绵宝宝模仿] “嘿，瑞奇和迪奇，
are you enjoying your time in Hollywood?"
你们在好莱坞玩得开心吗？”
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
[laughs] Pretty good, huh?
[笑] 挺不错的，对吧？
No. You know that's SpongeBob?
不。你知道那是海绵宝宝吗？
[Henchman] Where are they?
[手下] 他们在哪儿？
Someone's coming.
有人来了。
Hide!
躲起来！
[Henchman] Let's check in here.
我们在这里检查一下。
["Wipe Out" continues]
《Wipe Out》继续播放
[buzzer sounds] Time's up.
时间到了。
Step away from your plates.
离开你的盘子。
And now our fate is in the mouths of the judges.
现在我们的命运掌握在评委的口中。
[tense music]
紧张的音乐
Okay. You cooked.
好吧。你做了菜。
Dream of your life. Now let's go.
梦想你的生活。现在走吧。
No. I have to stay and see if I won.
不，我得留下来，看看我是否赢了。
Wow.
哇。
This octo ceviche is so good.
这个章鱼塞维奇太好吃了。
This one's good too.
这个也不错。
This one is amazing.
这个真是太棒了。
Give me some of that--
给我来点那个——
I'm gonna get some of yours too real quick, you know.
我也要马上尝尝你的。
Oh, Dad, you've got a little--
哦，爸爸，你嘴边有点——
[sucker pops] Oh!
[吸盘声] 哦！
Can you imagine if I beat Alex Guarnaschelli?
你能想象如果我打败了亚历克斯·瓜尔纳谢利会怎样吗？
This would be the best day of my life.
这将是我一生中最美好的一天。
Well, if we stay here it might also be the last.
好吧，如果我们留在这里，这也可能是最后一天。
We have to get out of here.
我们必须离开这里。
Just a few more seconds. I have to see if I won.
再等几秒钟。我得看看我是否赢了。
Just watch it on TV later.
晚点在电视上看吧。
How?
怎么？
I can't watch myself win this if I'm not here to win this.
如果我不在这里赢，我就无法看着自己赢。
You know, he's got a point, Dad.
你知道，他说的有道理，爸爸。
Yeah, well, so does that guy.
是啊，那个人也有道理。
And the winner is...
获胜者是...
Nicky Harper.
尼基·哈珀。
[cheering] Whoo-hoo!
[欢呼声] 哇呼！
Congratulations, Chef.
恭喜，厨师。
She called me "Chef!"
她叫我“厨师”！
We'll see you next time on Alex Guarnaschelli's
我们下次在亚历克斯·瓜尔纳谢利的
"Destination Cook Down."
“目的地烹饪大赛”再见。
[tropical music plays] [applause]
[热带音乐响起] [掌声]
[Direector] And cut!
[导演] 停！
[laughs]
[笑声]
Nowhere to run, Harpers.
无处可逃，哈珀一家。
You got us. You got us.
你抓到我们了。你抓到我们了。
We got the thumb drive right here.
我们拿到了U盘，就在这里。
Come and get it.
来拿吧。
Dad, give me my big spoon.
爸爸，给我我的大勺子。
Now?
现在吗？
Just trust me.
就相信我。
Ah!
啊！
Run!
跑！
[Dawn] Okay. Come on!
（Dawn）好的。快点！
[Jack] I hate octopus!
（Jack）我讨厌章鱼！
Dad, come on!
爸爸，快点！
So good.
真好吃。
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go!
走吧，走吧，走吧！
[Jack] Get this sucker off me!
杰克：把这个东西从我身上弄走！
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
[Ricky] Bless you.
瑞奇：保佑你。
Thank you.
谢谢。
[Dicky] Why do you have to be so polite?
迪基：你为什么一定要这么有礼貌？
[Anne] Boys, run!
安妮：男孩们，快跑！
[Tom] Guys, go, go, go!
汤姆：伙计们，快，快，快！
[Dawn] There's Mom!
妈妈在那儿！
[Tom] Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
[Anne] Thank goodness you're all right.
谢天谢地，你们都没事。
We're fine, but we barely escaped.
我们没事，但我们差点逃不出来。
Us too.
我们也是。
I won "Destination Cook Down!"
我赢了“目的地烹饪大赛”！
Good job.
干得好。
It was actually really awesome.
那实际上真的很棒。
Okay, we've got to go now.
好了，我们现在得走了。
Hey, hey. Costumes.
嘿，嘿。服装。
[Ricky] We can disguise ourselves!
[Ricky] 我们可以伪装自己！
[Tom] Yeah, let's go, let's go, let's go.
[Tom] 对，快走，快走，快走。
[Anne] Go, go, go.
[Anne] 快，快，快。
[Tom] Come on.
[Tom] 快点。
[all speaking at once]
[所有人同时说话]
Okay. All right. I'm just going to say it.
好吧。好吧。我直说了。
We look fabulous.
我们看起来棒极了。
[Dicky] Oh, I know.
[Dicky] 哦，我知道。
They're coming.
他们来了。
[Tom] Go! To the car!
[Tom] 快！上车！
[Dawn] Wait. I can't run in these heels.
等等，我穿这高跟鞋跑不了。
[Anne] Me neither.
我也是。
Me neither.
[Anne] Really?
真的吗？
Well, they're the only ones that fit.
嗯，只有这双合脚。
[Tom] Let's just go. Come on!
我们走吧，快点！
[Anne] Okay, okay, okay. Go!
好的，好的，走吧！
[Tom] Here. Take these.
这里，拿这些。
Ooh, do they have these in yellow?
哦，有黄色的吗？
Let's stop and look!
我们停下来看看！
No! Let's go. Come on! Really?
不！我们走吧。快点！真的吗？
Let's check in there.
我们去那边看看。
Alright! Out of my way! Me first! Me first!
好吧！别挡路！我先！我先！
Hey, to the left. To the left. No, no. The other left.
嘿，往左。往左。不，不。另一个左。
We're losing them guys.
我们要甩掉他们了。
Come on now.
快点。
Not a word.
一个字也别说。
Get my train.
帮我拦下那辆火车。
There's the car!
车在那儿！
[Dawn] Okay.
好的。
No! No, no, no!
不！不，不，不！
[Nicky] There goes the car.
[尼基] 车走了。
[Anne] See, I told you you weren't employee of the month, Tom.
[安妮] 看，我告诉过你，汤姆，你不是这个月的最佳员工。
[Man] And if you look to your left you might see
[男人] 如果你往左边看，你可能会看到
-I got this. -a weird, little kid running at me.
-我搞定这个。 -一个奇怪的小孩朝我跑来。
If you don't get out the next thing you'll see on your left is my right.
如果你不出去，接下来你左边看到的就是我的右边。
Not the face! Not the face!
别打脸！别打脸！
All right. Everybody out.
好吧。所有人都出去。
Come on!
快点！
[Jack] Hey!
[杰克] 嘿！
End of the line, Harpers!
到此为止了，哈珀一家！
[Tom] Uh-oh.
[汤姆]哎呀。
Oh, look. It's everybody's favorite, Thunderman.
哦，看。是大家最喜欢的，桑德曼。
Dr. Colosso?
科洛索博士？
No. Jack Griffo!
不。是杰克·格里菲！
That way! Which way?
那边！哪边？
Dibs! Can I get a selfie?
我先说的！我能拍个自拍吗？
[Tom] Let's go, let's go, let's go.
[汤姆]快走，快走，快走。
Get in. Get in. -Can I get one? -Yeah, of course.
上车。上车。 -我能拍一个吗？ -当然可以。
- All right. Okay.
- 好吧。好的。
Harpers out.
哈珀斯出去了。
- Hey! Get after them. I got autographs to sign.
- 嘿！追上他们。我还有签名要签。
[Tom] Get out of the way!
[汤姆] 让开！
I'll bet this isn't in the tour.
我打赌这不在行程里。
[dramatic music] [Dawn] Go, go, go!
[戏剧性音乐] [道恩] 快，快，快！
[Henchman] To the left! Go, go, go!
[手下] 向左！快，快，快！
Step on it! I'm going as fast as I can!
踩油门！我已经在尽全力了！
Well, go as fast as he can!
好吧，尽他所能快点！
[bicycle bell dings]
[自行车铃声]
There's a kid in a tricycle gaining on us.
有个骑三轮车的小孩在追我们。
Look at that sign!
看那个标志！
[Dawn] Thumb drive.
U盘。
That can't be a coincidence. Turn here!
这不可能是巧合。从这里转！
[All] Whoa!
哇！
Forget it. Let's get out and run.
算了。我们下车跑吧。
[Tom] No, no, no!
不，不，不！
[All] No!
不！
It's a dead end!
这是条死路！
We have to turn around.
我们得掉头。
Ah!
啊！
We can't.
我们不能。
[Anne] Run!
跑！
[Tom] Come on. Let's go.
来吧。我们走。
Go, go, go! Go!
快，快，快！快！
[Nicky] Up the hill!
上山！
[whimpers, screams]
（呜咽，尖叫）
You're really fast in those heels!
你穿高跟鞋跑得真快！
[Anne] I know. I know!
我知道。我知道！
[Nicky] This is worse than the Magic Castle driveway.
这比魔法城堡的车道还糟糕。
That was much steeper than this.
那比这陡多了。
No, it wasn't.
不，没有。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[Henchman] Harpers!
[手下]哈珀斯！
You might as well give up!
你们还是放弃吧！
Harpers never give up!
哈珀斯从不放弃！
Look. Gayle and his goons!
看，盖尔和他的打手们！
[Anne] How did they find us?
[安妮]他们是怎么找到我们的？
I want my thumb drive and my phone.
我要我的U盘和手机。
All my contacts are on there.
我所有的联系人都在上面。
[Dawn] We're surrounded!
[道恩]我们被包围了！
But I thought Dicky took them out!
但我想迪基已经把他们干掉了！
So did Dicky!
迪基也是这么想的！
I wish my shoes were yellow!
我希望我的鞋子是黄色的！
Quick! Up here!
快！这边！
[Anne] Go, go, go!
[安妮] 快，快，快！
[all panting]
[所有人喘气]
[Tom] They won't... find us... here.
[汤姆] 他们不会...找到我们...这里。
[Gayle] Follow that loud breathing.
[盖尔] 跟着那沉重的呼吸声。
We got to get out of here.me on.
我们得离开这里。
[Nicky] Maybe there's something in the bag that can help us.
[尼基] 也许包里有什么东西能帮我们。
[Dawn] Yeah.
是的。
The bag is empty!
包是空的！
Dicky, you thinking what I'm thinking?
迪基，你是不是在想我在想的事？
Sacrifice Dad to the bag gods and make a run for it?
牺牲爸爸给包神然后逃跑？
[Ricky] No.
不。
You can finally pull the cord.
你终于可以拉绳子了。
Now that I can I don't want to.
现在我可以了，但我不想。
Fine. Then don't pull the cord.
好吧。那别拉绳子。
You can't tell me what not to do.
你不能告诉我不能做什么。
What does that light mean?
那灯光是什么意思？
It means that.
这意味着。
[Tom] Holy floating thunder.
[汤姆] 天哪，漂浮的雷声。
[Dawn] Let's get out of here. Go, go, go!
[道恩] 我们离开这里。快，快，快！
[Anne] Everybody, hurry in.
[安妮] 大家，快进来。
[Tom] Come on!
[汤姆] 快点！
[Dawn] Go, go! Come on. Come on.
[道恩] 快，快！来吧。来吧。
Give me a boost, Anne.
给我一个助力，安妮。
[Anne] Oh.
[安妮] 哦。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[squeals] Go, go, go!
[尖叫声] 快，快，快！
Whoo!
哇！
[Gayle] Get them!
抓住他们！
[Tom] Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
Come on!
加油！
[all laugh]
大家都笑
Get over here.
过来这里。
What's the matter with you?
你怎么了？
[Ricky] Whoa. Isn't this so cool?
哇。这不是很酷吗？
[Anne] Oh, wow. Isn't it amazing, Tom?
哦，哇。这不是很惊人吗，汤姆？
Yeah. It's high, but it's beautiful.
是啊。虽然高，但是很美。
Guys, look.
伙计们，看。
We weren't hiding against a white wall.
我们不是躲在一堵白墙后面。
That was the Hollywood sign.
那是好莱坞标志。
[Boys] What?
什么？
[Tom] Awesome.
太棒了。
I can finally get my selfie.
我终于可以拍自拍照了。
♪ I won't waste another day ♪
♪ 我不会浪费另一天 ♪
♪ Wishing this would fade away ♪
♪ 希望这一切会消失 ♪
Oh, honey, it's perfect.
哦，亲爱的，这太完美了。
Not quite perfect.
还不算完美。
Everybody get in here. Come on.
大家过来这里。快点。
All right, ready?
好了，准备好了吗？
[Anne] Yeah.
（安妮）嗯。
And...
然后...
♪ I want a little bit of California ♪
♪ 我想要一点加州的感觉 ♪
[Ricky] Look, the Griffith Observatory!
（瑞奇）看，格里菲斯天文台！
♪ I wanna take my heart to the end of the world ♪
♪ 我想把我的心带到世界尽头 ♪
Oh, it's so cool.
哦，太酷了。
♪ And fly away tonight ♪
♪ 今晚我要飞走 ♪
♪ I want a little bit of open ocean ♪
♪ 我想要一点开阔的海洋 ♪
[Ricky] Look at the ferris wheel.
[Ricky] 看那个摩天轮。
♪ I wanna take my heart ♪ Oh, such a beautiful sunset.
♪ 我想带着我的心 ♪ 哦，多美的日落。
♪ And fly away, fly away tonight ♪
♪ 飞走吧，今晚就飞走 ♪
[Dicky] This is awesome.
[Dicky] 这太棒了。
♪ Fly away tonight ♪ [Dawn] Oh, my gosh, guys.
♪ 今晚飞走 ♪ [Dawn] 哦，天哪，伙计们。
Look, look, look!
看，看，看！
[Ricky] Whoa. Look at the view.
[Ricky] 哇。看这景色。
[Nicky] There's so many lights.
[Nicky] 这么多灯。
This keeps getting better and better.
越来越好了。
[overlapping agreements]
[重叠的赞同声]
So how are we going to get down?
那我们怎么下去？
I'm sure Mom knows how to do it.
妈妈肯定知道怎么做。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的，是的。
Mom has no idea how to do it.
妈妈根本不知道怎么做。
[all gasp]
[大家惊呼]
It may not matter how you do it,
可能怎么做并不重要，
because we're dropping fast.
因为我们正在快速下降。
Mom, pull the thingy!
妈妈，拉那个东西！
[Tom] Oh, the thingy's not working.
[汤姆]哦，那个东西不管用。
We're headed for the search lights.
我们正朝着探照灯飞去。
We're gonna crash on all those people!
我们就要撞上那些人了！
[Ricky] Maybe we'll hit that red carpet?
也许我们会落在红地毯上？
[Dicky] I hope it's soft.
希望那地毯够软。
Okay, before we crash I just want to say one thing.
好吧，在我们坠毁之前，我只想说一件事。
I love you guys.
我爱你们。
[All] And we love you too!
我们也爱你！
[all screaming]
（所有人尖叫）
[All] Oh.
哦。
Well, that wasn't so bad.
嗯，那也没那么糟糕。
I think we just landed
我觉得我们只是着陆了
in the middle of a movie premiere.
我们好像落在了电影首映式的中间。
Sweet.
太棒了。
They must think we're supposed to be here.
他们肯定以为我们该在这里。
Ah, what do we do?
啊，我们该怎么办？
Let's just get inside and think of our next move.
先进去，再想下一步。
Anne, exit boost.
安妮，加速离开。
Dicky doesn't need an "exit boost."
迪基不需要“加速离开”。
[camera shutters clicking]
[相机快门声]
[overlapping chatter]
[重叠的交谈声]
Oh, yeah. This feels right.
哦，没错。这感觉对了。
I think they think we're someone else.
我想他们以为我们是别人。
[Dawn] I don't care who they think we are.
[Dawn] 我不在乎他们以为我们是谁。
This is amazing.
这太神奇了。
Okay, kids, remember.
好了，孩子们，记住。
Strong diva base.
强大的天后基础。
Oh! Diva down.
哦！天后倒下了。
[Man] Oh. You all right, buddy?
[男人] 哦。你还好吗，伙计？
Just smile, and wave, and get inside. Come on.
只要微笑，挥手，然后进去。快点。
Okay.
好的。
We need to get to the police so we can end all of this.
我们需要去警察局，这样我们才能结束这一切。
I don't think that's going to happen.
我觉得那不会发生。
I want them found!
我要找到他们！
What, did they carpool?
什么，他们拼车吗？
Everybody duck.
大家都蹲下。
Crawl to a seat!
爬到座位上去！
[Dawn] Oh, my God. Here we go.
[Dawn] 哦，天哪。开始了。
[Jack] Check right there. Check him.
[Jack] 检查那里。检查他。
[Henchman] Open your jacket.
[Henchman] 打开你的夹克。
Oh, they're definitely going to see us.
哦，他们肯定会看到我们。
What are we gonna do?
我们该怎么办？
We have nowhere to go.
我们无处可逃。
Uh, guys?
呃，伙计们？
[all gasp] Olschewski!
奥尔舍夫斯基！
Oh, my gosh. Thank goodness.
哦，天哪。谢天谢地。
You know, you and I switched bags in the airport by accid--
你知道，我们在机场不小心换了包——
Shh.
嘘。
[epic music plays]
（史诗音乐播放）
We're going to Hollywood!
我们要去好莱坞！
[All] Whoo! Whoop, whoop, Hollywood.
（众人）喔！喔，喔，好莱坞。
Whoop, whoop, Hollywood. Whoop, whoop, Hollywood.
喔，喔，好莱坞。喔，喔，好莱坞。
[Dicky] Someone's flying a drone.
[迪基] 有人在飞无人机。
[laughs]
[笑声]
[Magician] Maybe you could help me?
[魔术师] 也许你能帮我？
[Ricky] Why don't you try and stop me.
[瑞奇] 你为什么不试试阻止我。
[Both] Three!
[两人] 三！
[Anne] Paramount Pictures.
[安妮] 派拉蒙影业。
This is so exciting.
这太令人兴奋了。
Isn't this exciting?
这不是很令人兴奋吗？
[Kids] Yeah, it really is.
[孩子们] 是的，真的很兴奋。
[soft orchestration]
[柔和的管弦乐]
Toast more tortillas.
再烤一些玉米饼。
Yes, Chef.
是的，主厨。
[Nicky] Season the peppers.
[尼基] 给辣椒调味。
[Dawn] Yes, Chef.
[道恩] 是的，主厨。
[Nicky] I've got the octopus.
[尼基] 我拿到了章鱼。
Nicky Harper.
尼基·哈珀。
Congratulations, Chef.
恭喜，主厨。
[gasps] She called me "Chef!"
[吸气声] 她叫我“主厨”！
Yes, it's me, Dawn Harper. The famous movie actress.
是的，是我，道恩·哈珀。那位著名的电影女演员。
[laughs] Please, no autographs.
[笑] 请，不要签名。
This is amazing.
这太不可思议了。
[Anne] Oh, it's perfect.
哦，太完美了。
[Dawn] Not quite perfect. Everybody get in here.
还不算完美。大家快进来。
[cheers and applause]
欢呼和掌声
Congratulations, Harpers.
祝贺你们，哈珀一家。
I'm sorry, but what the heck is going on?
对不起，但到底发生了什么？
Aren't you in Mexico right now?
你不是在墨西哥吗？
Everything that happened to you today
今天发生在你身上的一切
was by design from losing your luggage to the hot air balloon.
从丢失行李到热气球之旅，都是精心设计的。
It was all part of your ultimate family vacation.
这一切都是你终极家庭度假的一部分。
What? No way.
Awesome.
That is amazing.
Yeah. I mean it would be nice if we knew a little more
so we wouldn't be so freaked out, but... wow!
Wait, so is he Olschewski or not?
Oh, uh, I'm a cameraman.
Um, had to get close to you guys to get the shots and...
switch bags.
- Thank you. - [Gayle] Hey!
I hope you enjoyed your adventure.
我希望你们享受这次冒险。
Oh.
哦。
[All] Gayle?
盖尔？
It's "Danny," and it's a family name.
是'丹尼'，这是一个家族名字。
[all laugh]
（众人笑）
And...
而且...
[all gasp]
（众人惊呼）
We didn't want any member of your family to miss out,
我们不想让你们家族的任何成员错过，
so...
所以...
Get ready to smile for the pup-arazzi.
准备好为狗仔队微笑吧。
Oh, Squishy!
哦，小可爱！
[All] Squishy!
小可爱！
Jett Masterson?
杰特·马斯特森？
Dicky Harper?
迪基·哈珀？
[Both] Can I get your autograph?
能给我签个名吗？
Jinx.
金克丝。
Owe you a punch.
欠你一拳。
Boom!
砰！
This is unbelievable.
这真是难以置信。
Best vacation ever selfie.
有史以来最棒的度假自拍。
[all laugh]
[众人笑]
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ Counting down these seconds ♪
♪ 倒数这些秒 ♪
♪ Jumping off these fences ♪
♪ 跳过这些障碍 ♪
♪ Find another place to start again ♪
♪ 找到另一个地方 ♪ ♪ 重新开始 ♪
♪ The cracks in the sidewalk ♪
♪ 人行道上的裂缝 ♪
♪ I'm over all the small talk ♪
♪ 我厌倦了 ♪ ♪ 所有的闲聊 ♪
♪ Taking off like fire in the wind ♪
♪ 像风中的火一样 ♪ ♪ 起飞 ♪
- Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
- 嘿！嘿！嘿！嘿！
♪ I won't waste another day ♪
♪ 我不会浪费另一天 ♪
♪ Wishing this would fade away ♪
♪ 希望这一切会消失 ♪
♪ Running, we're not looking back ♪
♪ 奔跑，我们不再回头 ♪
♪ I want a little bit of California ♪
♪ 我想要一点加州的感觉 ♪
♪